Peter Siyak

email: p.sivak91@gmail.com Fairfield, CA +1-707-770-6743

<u>(sivo91.github.io)</u> updated: 01/01/2022

<u>Document (sivo91.github.io)</u> <u>https://peter-sivak.webs.com/</u>

EDUCATION

EUROPE: Elementary School Slovakia, EU 09/1986 - 05/1994

Business Academy Slovakia, EU 09/1994 - 05/1998

USA: GED Tulsa, OK and Napa, CA 2019

Full time student (Completed 57.5 Units, current GPA = 4.00)

Web DevelopmentSolano Community College, Fairfield, Ca2020 – ongoingWeb DevelopmentSanta Rosa Junior College, Santa Rosa, Ca2020 – ongoing

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Seeking entry level position in Web development.

Hardworking, dedicated retired professional athlete with winning attitude who delivers on goals – literally -is preparing for the next chapter in life to become front end Web developer.

My goal is to remain productive member of our family and continue to achieve success in life, to become a leader and recognized expert in a field of computer science. I believe Information Technology is going to play even greater role in our life than it does now, beyond our wildest imagination.

The past twenty years had taught me how to succeed and shine in crowd, taught me resilience and discipline. I learned to fight for every moment and learn to keep winning momentum.

My past career molded my hard-working character and righteous personality. I am used to work under pressure and deliver consistent work in the least amount of time.

These attributes allowed me to achieve success and win championships and numerous personal awards. Although, my previous career is over and it soon becomes a warm but distant memory, I look forward to a bright future and challenges that a field of computer science will bring.

QUALIFICATIONS

Web Interactivity

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

C++ Fundamentals

Visual Basic

Microcomputer Application

Game Coding (2d Phaser3, 3d Three.JS, 3d PlayCanvas)

Web Development1 (HTML, CSS)

Web Development2 (Bootstrap, WordPress) *current
Web Development3 (Javascript, jQuerty, D3.js, Vue.js) *current
Multimedia For the Web *current

Blender (3d Design)

UDEMY : John Smilga(JS), Traversy Media(JS)

WORK EXPERIENCES

FedEx delivery, part-time

06/12/2020 - ongoing

Daily exceeding metrics 15/ pkgs/h averaging 22 pkgs/h in the shortest time



Professional hockey player

I was forward, yet universal -playing in all situations- on the first line, first power-play unit and killing penalties and helping the defense

I was a high scorer, yet my priority was team success -I always passed the puck to teammate who had better chance to score

I worked hard- after game or practice, I still added conditioning on the ground

EUROPE

| • | HK 32 Liptovsky Mikulas | Liptovsky Mikulas, Slovakia, | 09/1999 - 03/2001 |
|---|-------------------------|------------------------------|---------------------|
| • | HK Dukla Trencin | Trencin, Slovakia, | 09, 2001 - 04, 2007 |
| • | MSHK Zilina | Zilina, Slovakia, | 09,2006-04,2008 |
| • | HK Zlin | Zlin, Czech Republic, | 09,2008-04,2011 |
| • | MSHK Zilina | Zilina, Slovakia, | 09/2011 - 04/2012 |

USA

| CDE | <u> </u> | | |
|-----|------------------------------|--------------------|-------------------|
| • | SF Bulls, ECHL | San Francisco, CA, | 10/2012 - 04/2012 |
| • | Alaska Aces, ECHL | Anchorage, AK, | 10/2013 - 06/2014 |
| • | Stockton Thunder, ECHL | Stockton, CA, | 10/2014 - 01/2014 |
| • | Orlando Solar Bears, ECHL | Orlando, FL, | 02/2014 -04/2014 |
| • | Fort Wayne Komets, ECHL | Fort Wayne, IN, | 10/2015 - 12/2015 |
| • | Alaska Aces, ECHL | Anchorage, AK, | 12/2015 - 04/2016 |
| • | Alaska Aces, ECHL | Anchorage, AK, | 10/2016 - 04/2017 |
| • | Utah Grizllies, ECHL | Salt Lake City, UT | 10/2016 - 10/2016 |
| • | Rapid City Rush, ECHL | Rapid City, SD, | 10/2016 - 04/2017 |
| • | Worchester Sharks, AHL | Worchester, MA, | 03/2013 - 05/2013 |
| • | Bridgeport Sound Tigers, AHL | Bridgeport, CT, | 11/2014 - 12/2014 |
| • | Tulsa Oilers, ECHL | Tulsa, OK, | 10/2018 - 04/2019 |

CANADA

Abbotsford Heat, AHL Abbotsford 09/2013 - 10/2013



Assistant coach

Recording, analyzing, highlighting individual players stats during the game, game situations, teaching on -ice, off-ice to improve strategy to win the games

Tulsa Oilers, ECHL

Tulsa, OK,

10/2018 - 04/2019

LANGUAGES

English – good Slovak - excellent Czech – excellent

AWARDS

| Slovak Extraliga National Champion | 1 st Place EU | 2003 - 2004 |
|-------------------------------------|--------------------------|-------------|
| Slovak Extraliga | 3 rd Place EU | 2004 - 2005 |
| Slovak Extraliga | 2 nd Place EU | 2006 - 2007 |
| | | |
| ECHL Kelly Cup Champion ALASKA Aces | 1st Place, USA | 2013 - 2014 |

Personal awards

ECHL Performer of the Year (+49)

ECHL Sportsmanship Award (10 PM)- honors the player judged "to have exhibited the best type of sportsmanship and gentlemanly conduct with a high standard of playing ability."

| ECHL ALL-STAR Team | | 2015 - 2016 |
|--------------------|----------------------------|-------------|
| ECHL ALL-STAR Team | NHL network televised game | 2016 - 2017 |

LINKS

sivo91 (Peter) (github.com)

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter Siv%C3%A1k

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MYR07WEBbPg

https://www.eliteprospects.com/player/34714/peter-sivak

https://www.hockeydb.com/ihdb/stats/pdisplay.php?pid=57465

CURIOSITY

The scorer of one of the fastest goals in hockey history. 4:08

The fastest goal in Hockey,00:04:08 sec. Peter Sivak - YouTube



Any statistics wizards out there? I want to know the odds of picking the correct hockey player to score a goal at an exact time during a single period of hockey.

Back in the day we had a promotion with the IBEW local 1547 and you had to guess the player and that player would have to score a goal at 15:47 of the second period.

We had a guy actually do it when he picked Peter Peter Sivák to score that goal.

What are the odds of that?

Thank you.

Also, if anyone knows who that guy was that won please let me know.

Thank you.

| Most relevan | | ∟ Like | Comment Comment | A | Share | | |
|-----------------|---|-----------------|-----------------|---|-----------|------|------|
| | | | | | Most rele | evar | nt 🕶 |
| Write a comment | 7 | Write a comment | | | © @ | GF) | 0 |

